<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Academic</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Academic</title>
      <link>https://example.com/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>https://example.com/talk/example-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/talk/example-talk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further event details, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;page elements&lt;/a&gt; such as image galleries, can be added to the body of this page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating presentations</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/presentations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-dozen-slides&#34;&gt;A Dozen Slides&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ve all sat through &amp;ndash; and given &amp;ndash; presentations with too many PowerPoint slides. Moreover, we’ve all toyed with the various ways of trying to make complex theories, long quotable quotes from scholars or field observations, or enormous statistical tables into a single overhead screen. Many of us have also seen the guidelines and op-eds about what a good PowerPoint slide looks like, but few academics have a budget for a designer to really help with graphic elements. Moreover, the presentation of original research (or even proposals for original research) is different from the style and content of presenting with PowerPoint in the corporate world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what is a good starting point for a basic first draft of a presentation for any circumstance in which you are presenting your own research? What would work across audiences, whether you are presenting to a group of students in a classroom, peer researchers at a conference, prospective colleagues at a job talk, or the public?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good way to start is by imagining a dozen slides. Obviously, the content that goes into this outline will vary, depending on whether you are doing quantitative, comparative, qualitative or humanistic inquiry. But this outline should be flexible enough to serve you in a short conference presentation or a long job talk: the basic goals and ingredients are the same. Indeed you may find that this outline exposes some of the shared assumption about what research can be across the humanities or the natural, physical and social sciences. Like an essay, there are some standard ingredients that research presentations should have. Some disciplines have their own conventions and your mentors should coach you on what these are. But not having the basic ingredients risks communicating that you have not been fully professionalized as a researcher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;less-is-more&#34;&gt;Less Is More&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is an old adage that good data visualizations have a low ink-to-data ratio. You want every drop of ink to communicate something meaningful, and bedazzling colors or animations detract from what you want to communicate. Similarly, after you chose a background color for your presentation, only add pixels of text and color to communicate information. If the pixel is communicating something that you will be saying out loud during the presentation, it may not be needed. If playing with pixels is more about design than data, you are simply decorating your ideas and evidence. And Orwell’s writing rules can be adapted for conference presentations and job talks:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never use a metaphor, simile or other figure of speech that you are used to seeing in print or saying colloquially.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never use a long word where a short one will do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If it is possible to cut a word out, always cut it out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never use the passive where you can use the active.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Never use a foreign phrase, a scientific word or a jargon word if you can think of an everyday English equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Break any of these rules before presenting anything outright barbarous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Practically speaking, this means it is OK for you to edit quotes and use ellipses or hard brackets as necessary. It is OK to just present part of a model &amp;ndash; no need to put the variables you aren’t going to discuss up on the screen, just mention in passing that they were part of the analysis (people will understand that you can return to them in Q&amp;amp;A).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;its-a-performance&#34;&gt;It’s a Performance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is just an outline structure. The design elements are up to you, as is the performance. If you use a laser slide pointer, hold it in your hand and rest your hand on the corner of the podium so the red dot looks stable on the screen. Trace lines slowly on the screen: from the audience point of view, a quick jittery slash of laser across the screen just makes you look nervous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Minimize the animations and don’t embed video &amp;ndash; they break the audience’s attention from you. Soft gentle fade-ins look good; fast-moving swiping transitions with silly sound effects are distracting. If you are studying visual culture and are analyzing a single, important video artifact, it might be OK to stop your formal presentation and let the audience watch the object of your inquiry. But inserting YouTube joke videos, excerpts from other people’s lectures or recordings from a field site means you are surrendering the attention. Unless you do a full setup and then analysis of an embedded video it is rarely worth jarring your audience and giving up the minutes you have to present your ideas … and you risk that the audience will fixate on the video and interpret it in unexpected ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use one or two slides that are just a picture &amp;ndash; the kind of picture that is provocative and can trigger a whole slew of thoughts from you. An image that helps prompt you in some way that the audience will remember. As a presenter, this should let you get animated and let the audience see that you can eloquently riff on your research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use one or two slides that are just text. Big text so that people can read with you, and it&amp;rsquo;s OK if you read the text out loud. Chose well-phrased lines from your writing that have precisely chosen words and bring home a punch line. Use this presentation style sparingly. This should let you hammer home the most important point of your research, using the crafted language that communicates the key thing you want to communicate. Again, these should be the ideas you don’t want your audience to misinterpret.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;play-with-outline-after-each-performance&#34;&gt;Play With Outline After Each Performance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the long term, your slide deck can include other slides that you have in waiting should you need more content either to help answer audience questions or fill in the time. Indeed the more you practice, the better able you will be to collapse or stretch your presentation of your ideas. So if you ever design a good slide but decide there may not be enough time for it, don’t delete it, just move it to the very bottom, where you can put it up if needed during the Q&amp;amp;A.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you are practiced with this slide show, you will also feel comfortable introducing your own variations. But it is good to start with this outline. Since the slides described above are also the common components of research projects across the disciplines, if you drop one in a presentation to a scholarly audience someone will probably query you about it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;starter-outline&#34;&gt;Starter Outline&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;title-slide-1&#34;&gt;Title (Slide 1)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snappy title, substantive subtitle. Date, your name, email address, department and college or university affiliation. Perhaps the logo of your home institution and your funder if relevant. This should be up first, as people ready settle in for your brilliant talk. By the way, always introduce yourself &amp;ndash; don’t just launch into your material!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;outline-of-my-talk-slide-2&#34;&gt;Outline of My Talk (Slide 2)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tell us what’s ahead with an outline. Make sure the section titles in the outline appear in the same phrasing later on so that the audience can track where you are. Roman numerals can signal progress in the argument, and some people put a running header on slides along with slide number. You don’t need the date, your name or your institution’s name on every slide. Those pixels are redundant after your first slide and introducing yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;me-and-my-research-slide-3&#34;&gt;Me and My Research (Slide 3)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give us a few quick reminders about who you are, who you’ve collaborated with, how you came to (or fell into) this topic, or why you are personally invested in this research. If you are proud of having received some financial support for the research, or of having made it through the human subjects’ approval process, some of those details can appear on the slide. This slide helps people locate your research in the network of funders, research centers and other scholars involved in this area of inquiry. This slide also establishes your credibility and teaches the audience about your interests. You can also discuss a previous paper or previous project, which would build a bridge to the next slide. While the slide can identify your formal ties to the research community, this can also be the moment to take people behind the stage and tell them the personal compelling story that really drew you into the project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;research-questions-slide-4&#34;&gt;Research Questions (Slide 4)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This slide should clearly state the research questions. Some people, especially those doing comparative or quantitative research, may also have working hypotheses. But all of us have research questions. Moreover, this slide will get lots of editing over time as you come across better words to substitute and as your research agenda evolves. Ideally your research interests can be expressed several ways: first through a big-picture research question that will be abstract and general, broadly appealing, even, and understandable for people who aren’t experts in your subfield or who are interested in your theory ideas but not really your specific case study or research domain; second, through a more focused question that is specific to your period of inquiry, your case study, your population, your sample or your artifact. For example, this might be the difference between “What does the concentration of media ownership mean for deliberative democracy?” and “What were the causes and consequences of the concentration of television broadcast licenses in the United States between 1990 and 2008?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While this slide is up, you also have a unique opportunity to intrigue the audience with a weird problem, a perplexing quote, a puzzling situation. The details of the narrative don’t need to go on the slide &amp;ndash; you entrance us with an oxymoron, riddle or highly problematic quote from your text or your fieldwork. Or an unresolved question that your peers have missed. It should be something that will make someone in the audience heckle “no!” or “neat!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;literature-review-and-existing-knowledge-slide-5&#34;&gt;Literature Review and Existing Knowledge (Slide 5)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these two slides, you present the ways in which other contemporary researchers would tackle your research questions, solve your puzzle or deconstruct your artifact. This slide shows the audience that you are on top of the literature, and that you have done due diligence in assessing other schools of thought and familiarized yourself with other people’s critiques. Convince us that you know what the existing research is, but don’t go overboard. Don’t dwell on the literature review, just convince us that you know it, and if any of the important researchers are in the audience this is an opportunity to quickly acknowledge their contributions. This may vary a bit in the humanities, but on the whole the audience is not at your research talk to hear about Habermas, Foucault, Bourdieu, Castells, Einstein or Dawkins, they are there to learn about your work. If your work is on their work, you can refer to big names, but spending time on other people’s ideas means less time on your ideas. Slide 5 should be about what the leading scholars might say on your research question and about what others might say &amp;ndash; either some dissenters or some people who recently and directly tried to answer your research question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;possible-answers-and-rival-theories-slides-6-and-7&#34;&gt;Possible Answers and Rival Theories (Slides 6 and 7)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this slide, you summarize three different yet plausible answers to your research question. You transition from theorizing about how other thinkers might answer your question to the most plausible answers. Of course refer to the literature and scholars you assessed, and perhaps summarize two rival explanations and suggest that you have a third, better, more nuanced answer. This is the bridge to the next series of slides, and it shows that you have identified a puzzle that current scholarship can’t solve or doesn’t handle well, and that you feel confident enough about your solution and handling of the puzzle to warrant presenting your work. If some of the people behind the rival theories are in the audience, be respectful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-methods-slide-8&#34;&gt;My Methods (Slide 8)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Slide 8 should be about methods choices. Say things like, “To complete this research I have spent [X years of my life] doing [fieldwork/lab work/archival work/statistical analysis]. I have traveled to [these cities or libraries], interviewed [X number of experts], created [original datasets/original compositions/original artwork].” Detail your research process, especially if the audience is full of researchers. Impress the audience with the volume of artifacts you’ve studied, number people you’ve talked to, time you have dedicated or places you’ve been. By now, you are one of the world’s experts on your research domain, so describe all the evidence you’ve been working on and the kinds of intellectual work you’ve put into becoming this expert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-findings-slides-9-and-10&#34;&gt;My Findings (Slides 9 and 10)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your more nuanced understanding of the problem at hand is based on your expertise: your fieldwork, your considered assessment of a media text, your collection and assessment of data, or your cross-case comparison. You get to justify your methodological and epistemological approach, and do your reading of evidence. There is a lot of variety about what can go in these slides, but they can be dedicated to you or your project. These slides can be about findings from your specific field site, artifact or data analysis. In other words, they should be the answers you would offer to your second very specific research question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;conclusions-and-next-steps-slide-11&#34;&gt;Conclusions and Next Steps (Slide 11)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this slide, you can suggest that more work is needed in this domain. Perhaps there are some remaining aspects of the research question that you couldn’t quite get to, or something about your sampling strategy that might have biased the outcomes. Perhaps your conclusions lead inexorably to more questions, and you could identify some of these … especially if your intention is to go on with this or if you want to influence the trajectory of other researchers in the room. This penultimate slide allows you to answer the big-picture question, and it should summarize the takeaway ideas that will interest even people who don’t care about your particular case study. They can be simply stated, but like your slide of research questions, they will take a lot of drafting and redrafting. Indeed, you may rephrase your conclusions the night before a presentation, to highlight conclusions you expect your audience will be particularly interested in. This is where you can say big things about the intellectual merit or broad impact of your work. What are takeaway ideas one, two and three?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;references-slide-12&#34;&gt;References (Slide 12)&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn’t about referencing other people’s work, it is about your work and it should identify some of the writing you’ve done in this domain. It doesn’t only have to list published items, it can list working papers, co-authored articles or manuscripts that are forthcoming, under review or in preparation. It is great if you have an authored or co-authored piece on the topic you are presenting on. But when most of us are presenting new research it hasn’t come out in print, so as long as your references are relevant to the research they should be identified here. If you haven’t actually published, then perhaps list your team members and move the funder information from the early slide to this slide. Repeat your identifying information from the first slide, and then list two or three items or the URL of a website where people could find out more about your work. This slide can stay up during the question and answer period, and it is much better than a final slide that says “good-bye,” “thank you” or worse, “fin.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report of the week from 05.15 to 05.21</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/past-week-report-05.21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/past-week-report-05.21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-week&#34;&gt;The week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The renderer project is close to being completely done. Some things just need to be ironed out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Markup Languages</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/markup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/markup/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-a-markup-language&#34;&gt;What is a markup language?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lightweight markup language is a modern system for annotating a document in a way that is syntactically distinguishable from the text, and designed with a simple readable syntax. In fact, the syntax is so basic that anyone can quickly learn to use these markup languages. The key advantage of this type of language is that it is designed to be easy to enter the annotated text in a text editor, and at the same time easy to follow the document source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This type of language has plain text formats, with very simple special characters or strings that mark up section headers, lists, tables, link syntax, font faces and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a number of uses for lightweight markup languages. We live in a world where there is a constant stream of emails, memos, articles, reports, and tweets. Many people write, rearrange and reuse text. Lightweight markup languages are helpful in this regard, saving lots of time over hand-crafted HTML tags, speeding up any writing-related process. They also are particularly strong where the reader wants to read the document source as well as the output. Moreover, they are frequently used in web-based publishing, including wikis and weblogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By using these open source tools, individuals can produce high quality annotated text within a few minutes, and at no cost at all. The code is portable, and can be output to documents in a wide array of formats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s explore the 9 lightweight markup languages at hand. For each title we have compiled its own portal page, a full description with an in-depth analysis of its features, together with links to relevant resources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Language&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Description&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Markdown&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Markup language and Text-to-HTML conversion tool&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;MultiMarkdown&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Based on Markdown with additional features&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;GigHub Flavored Markdown&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;For user content on GitHub.com and GitHub Enterprise&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Markdown Extra&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Lightweight markup language based on Markdown&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;AsciiDoc&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Presentable text document format for writing articles&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Textile&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Billed as a &amp;ldquo;humane web text generator&amp;rdquo;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Texy&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Text-to-XHTML formatter and converter library&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tome&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Markup Language and Tool Suite for Authors&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;reStructuredText&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Markup Syntax and Parser Component of Docutils&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report of the week from 05.08 to 05.14</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/past-week-report-05.14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/past-week-report-05.14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-week&#34;&gt;The week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The development of the 3D Engine mentioned in the previous post is in full swing. I have a good feeling I will be able to finish it during the next week.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD concepts</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/ci-cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/ci-cd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;definition&#34;&gt;Definition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CI and CD stand for continuous integration and continuous delivery/continuous deployment. In very simple terms, CI is a modern software development practice in which incremental code changes are made frequently and reliably. Automated build-and-test steps triggered by CI ensure that code changes being merged into the repository are reliable. The code is then delivered quickly and seamlessly as a part of the CD process. In the software world, the CI/CD pipeline refers to the automation that enables incremental code changes from developers’ desktops to be delivered quickly and reliably to production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-is-cicd-important&#34;&gt;Why is CI/CD important?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CI/CD allows organizations to ship software quickly and efficiently. CI/CD facilitates an effective process for getting products to market faster than ever before, continuously delivering code into production, and ensuring an ongoing flow of new features and bug fixes via the most efficient delivery method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-difference-between-ci-and-cd&#34;&gt;What is the difference between CI and CD?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuous integration (CI) is practice that involves developers making small changes and checks to their code. Due to the scale of requirements and the number of steps involved, this process is automated to ensure that teams can build, test, and package their applications in a reliable and repeatable way. CI helps streamline code changes, thereby increasing time for developers to make changes and contribute to improved software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuous delivery (CD) is the automated delivery of completed code to environments like testing and development. CD provides an automated and consistent way for code to be delivered to these environments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuous deployment is the next step of continuous delivery. Every change that passes the automated tests is automatically placed in production, resulting in many production deployments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continuous deployment should be the goal of most companies that are not constrained by regulatory or other requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In short, CI is a set of practices performed as developers are writing code, and CD is a set of practices performed after the code is completed.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report of the week from 05.01 to 05.07</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/past-week-report-05.07/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/past-week-report-05.07/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-week&#34;&gt;The week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the week I began working on a simple 3D engine using Java Swing.
It is still in development so we will see what will come out of it later.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>https://example.com/slides/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/slides/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;create-slides-in-markdown-with-wowchemy&#34;&gt;Create slides in Markdown with Wowchemy&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Wowchemy&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&#34;https://owchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;code&gt;E&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34; data-lang=&#34;python&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;n&#34;&gt;porridge&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;blueberry&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;if&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;n&#34;&gt;porridge&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;==&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;blueberry&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;    &lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s2&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;Eating...&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  Three
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Only the speaker can read these notes
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;-&lt;/span&gt; Press &lt;span class=&#34;sb&#34;&gt;`S`&lt;/span&gt; key to view
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  {{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;

&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/media/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34; data-lang=&#34;markdown&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;background-image&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;/media/boards.jpg&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;background-color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;#0000FF&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;{{&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;slide&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;na&#34;&gt;class&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s&#34;&gt;&amp;#34;my-style&amp;#34;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;}}
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34; data-lang=&#34;css&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;o&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nc&#34;&gt;reveal&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;section&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nt&#34;&gt;h3&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;  &lt;span class=&#34;k&#34;&gt;color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;kc&#34;&gt;navy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/discussions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Project</title>
      <link>https://example.com/project/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/project/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Duis posuere tellus ac convallis placerat. Proin tincidunt magna sed ex sollicitudin condimentum. Sed ac faucibus dolor, scelerisque sollicitudin nisi. Cras purus urna, suscipit quis sapien eu, pulvinar tempor diam. Quisque risus orci, mollis id ante sit amet, gravida egestas nisl. Sed ac tempus magna. Proin in dui enim. Donec condimentum, sem id dapibus fringilla, tellus enim condimentum arcu, nec volutpat est felis vel metus. Vestibulum sit amet erat at nulla eleifend gravida.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nullam vel molestie justo. Curabitur vitae efficitur leo. In hac habitasse platea dictumst. Sed pulvinar mauris dui, eget varius purus congue ac. Nulla euismod, lorem vel elementum dapibus, nunc justo porta mi, sed tempus est est vel tellus. Nam et enim eleifend, laoreet sem sit amet, elementum sem. Morbi ut leo congue, maximus velit ut, finibus arcu. In et libero cursus, rutrum risus non, molestie leo. Nullam congue quam et volutpat malesuada. Sed risus tortor, pulvinar et dictum nec, sodales non mi. Phasellus lacinia commodo laoreet. Nam mollis, erat in feugiat consectetur, purus eros egestas tellus, in auctor urna odio at nibh. Mauris imperdiet nisi ac magna convallis, at rhoncus ligula cursus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cras aliquam rhoncus ipsum, in hendrerit nunc mattis vitae. Duis vitae efficitur metus, ac tempus leo. Cras nec fringilla lacus. Quisque sit amet risus at ipsum pharetra commodo. Sed aliquam mauris at consequat eleifend. Praesent porta, augue sed viverra bibendum, neque ante euismod ante, in vehicula justo lorem ac eros. Suspendisse augue libero, venenatis eget tincidunt ut, malesuada at lorem. Donec vitae bibendum arcu. Aenean maximus nulla non pretium iaculis. Quisque imperdiet, nulla in pulvinar aliquet, velit quam ultrices quam, sit amet fringilla leo sem vel nunc. Mauris in lacinia lacus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suspendisse a tincidunt lacus. Curabitur at urna sagittis, dictum ante sit amet, euismod magna. Sed rutrum massa id tortor commodo, vitae elementum turpis tempus. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Aenean purus turpis, venenatis a ullamcorper nec, tincidunt et massa. Integer posuere quam rutrum arcu vehicula imperdiet. Mauris ullamcorper quam vitae purus congue, quis euismod magna eleifend. Vestibulum semper vel augue eget tincidunt. Fusce eget justo sodales, dapibus odio eu, ultrices lorem. Duis condimentum lorem id eros commodo, in facilisis mauris scelerisque. Morbi sed auctor leo. Nullam volutpat a lacus quis pharetra. Nulla congue rutrum magna a ornare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliquam in turpis accumsan, malesuada nibh ut, hendrerit justo. Cum sociis natoque penatibus et magnis dis parturient montes, nascetur ridiculus mus. Quisque sed erat nec justo posuere suscipit. Donec ut efficitur arcu, in malesuada neque. Nunc dignissim nisl massa, id vulputate nunc pretium nec. Quisque eget urna in risus suscipit ultricies. Pellentesque odio odio, tincidunt in eleifend sed, posuere a diam. Nam gravida nisl convallis semper elementum. Morbi vitae felis faucibus, vulputate orci placerat, aliquet nisi. Aliquam erat volutpat. Maecenas sagittis pulvinar purus, sed porta quam laoreet at.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An example conference paper</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publication/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/publication/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Click the &lt;em&gt;Cite&lt;/em&gt; button above to demo the feature to enable visitors to import publication metadata into their reference management software.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    Create your slides in Markdown - click the &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; button to check out the example.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes can be added here, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;code, math, and images&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://example.com/admin/config.yml</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/admin/config.yml</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
